Mihael Evđenić

Frontend Developer - student

+385917207707

Zagreb, Hrvatska

SUMMARY

I am currently a full-time fifth-year student of electrical engineering at the Zagreb University of Applied Sciences, majoring in automation and process computing. In September 2021, I completed my undergraduate professional studies in electrical engineering at the Zagreb University of Applied Sciences, majoring in automation and process computing. During this three-year study, I gained general knowledge of the C programming language, electronic components, analog and digital circuits, microcontrollers, programmable logic controllers, as well as general knowledge of electrical engineering.

At work, I am collegial, a team player, I like a positive working environment and communication, but also constructive criticism. I am also motivated and eager to develop my programming knowledge.

EXPERIENCE

Waiter 05/2022 - 08/2022

Globalna Hrana d.o.o.

- · General bar work
- · Preparing drinks
- · Keeping the bar clean
- Serving and communicating with guests

Waiter 06/2020 - 10/2020

Me Gusta Bar

- · General bar work
- Preparing drinks
- · Keeping the bar clean
- · Serving and communicating with guests

Digital content editor 07/2018 - 10/2019

Školska knjiga d.d.

- · Production and editing of digital, educational and interactive content
- · Working in a team, coordination with different subject editors
- HTML

Warehouse worker

Sport Vision d.o.o.

General warehouse work

06/2017 - 08/2017

EDUCATION

Automation and process computing

Zagreb University of Applied Sciences - Bachelor's degree in electrical engineering

· Programming language C

- Microcontrollers
- Programmable logic controllers Simatic S7

10/2017 - Present

- Analog and digital circuits
- Application of personal computers
- MATLAB Simulink

SKILLS

React	Basic	JQuery	Basic
HTML	Basic	С	Basic
CSS	Basic	Visual Studio Code	Basic
SCSS	Basic	MATLAB - Simulink	Intermediate
JavaScript	Basic	MS Office	Intermediate

LANGUAGES

Croatian	Native	English	Fluent	
----------	--------	---------	--------	--